Rika, did you eat salt milk?
No, I didn't.
Me neither.
Then, me too.
Wait, wait.
Moeka, you're so cute.
You're so cute.
Rika, you're so cute.
You look like you're eating salt milk.
Yeah.
Rika, you're so cute.
Hello, everyone.
Shut up!
I'm Yano Moeka from Nogizaka 46.
I'm a 6th grader.
Well, for some reason,
I'm sliding on the slide.
You're so fast.
I'm so fast.
I'm eating salt milk.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
Nogizaka 46.
A full-fledged tour in the summer of 2025.
A PR battle.
Yay!
Good job.
My butt is itching.
Yeah, it must have been hot.
My blood circulation is getting better.
It's okay.
It's about 35 degrees Celsius today.
It's hot.
We're in Miyagi Prefecture right now.
This is where we're going to perform.
There's a Super Arena behind us.
Yada, you've been to this slide before, right?
That's right.
When I was in elementary school,
I came to this park with my friend's family in Miyagi.
We came here and played.
Really?
That's what I heard.
So I came here because it's a place of memories.
This time, we're going to go around our memories and places we wanted to go.
I'm sure the fans will come here for the live performance.
For that, we're going to PR the surrounding area of Miyagi Prefecture.
In the end, we're going to map the recommended places we've been to.
I'd like to go around a lot.
Also, we're going to put up posters in the store we've been to.
We're going to make the summer of Mugi-zaka more exciting.
Let's do our best and have fun.
I'll do my best.
It's hot.
Let's go.
We're heading to the first store.
This is the place of Yodachan's memories, isn't it?
That's right.
I was with my friend's family in Miyagi.
We bought bread here and ate it together in the park.
That's right.
That's nice.
The park just now?
That's right.
I've been here dozens of times.
It's a park.
I've been watching your eating log.
I had a lot of fun until I got here today.
I heard that wasabi bacon cheese is very strong.
Wasabi is quite strong.
It says it's a renewal.
That's right.
Moeka has started to act on her own.
She acts on her own before eating.
Moeka, Moeka, Moeka.
I remember eating sandwiches at this store.
Let's watch it together.
The grape bread looks delicious.
It's cute.
It looks delicious.
Let's take a picture.
Let's go.
Let's take a picture together.
I think the gyukuro burger is delicious.
There's a burger too.
It looks delicious.
There are a lot of burgers.
That's great.
This is my youth.
I always ate this when there was an event at Hexheim.
It's nostalgic.
It looks like a picnic.
It's just right.
This is delicious too.
It's delicious.
What should we do?
We're having too much fun.
Let's take a picture.
It's crispy.
It looks delicious.
Let's do our best.
Let's eat as much as we can.
Let's eat.
It's good.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It's cute.
It's very delicious.
It has a lot of chicken.
It's thick.
It's delicious.
It's not dry.
It's cute.
Let's eat.
The bread is delicious.
It's cute.
It's very delicious.
It's like a massage.
It's like that.
It's crispy.
It's very delicious.
Can I check the hole in the bread?
There is a hole.
It's important to make a hole.
It's difficult to make a hole.
You can't make a hole by kneading.
It's delicious.
It looks delicious.
It's cute.
Hikari is eating cutely.
How is it?
It's cute.
It doesn't blink.
It has a lot of eyes.
It's delicious.
What is this?
It looks like a herb.
It's delicious.
It's different from salt.
I feel the saltiness.
It's delicious.
It's chewy.
It's crispy.
This is difficult.
I'm worried about you.
It's delicious.
It's cute.
Is it delicious?
I like cream cheese.
This cream cheese is delicious.
It has a lot of cinnamon.
It's delicious.
I like it.
It's cute.
It's delicious.
This time, on August 2nd,
Nogizaka 46 will have a live performance at Sekisui Haim.
Can I put this poster on?
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
I want you to put it there.
Is it okay?
Thank you.
I will put it on.
Is it around here?
It's around there.
Is it straight?
It's right.
It looks good.
Thank you.
Thank you for your attention.
I'm happy.
Next is Rika.
I have never been to this store.
I looked at the store on the map.
It looks delicious.
It's perfect for this season.
I want to come here.
It was close to the store.
It's close to the store.
It's natural.
This is the best location.
It's almost there.
It looks delicious.
I'm happy.
It's a big surprise.
I was surprised.
You prepared a happy birthday for me.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
I like you already.
I like you before you enter the store.
You are kind.
I'm coming.
Hello.
It's amazing.
It looks delicious.
Wait a minute.
Isn't it this?
This is it.
It's a gelato.
There are so many kinds of gelato.
Do you want to make it double?
I want to make it double.
Let's make it double.
The first order.
I'm nervous.
It's a peach milk.
I'm thinking about two options.
I've decided.
Rika has decided.
It's a friend.
I'm really not good at this.
Let's think together.
I've decided.
The first order.
I'm thinking about two options.
It's a pear milk.
Please listen to me.
I was thinking about strawberry milk.
I'm going to drink it.
Let's make it a strawberry milk.
It looks delicious.
It's peach and pear milk.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
What did you eat?
I ate a pear milk.
Is the strawberry strong?
It's strong strawberry.
Is the pear milk delicious?
Yes.
It's rich.
What did you eat?
It's peach.
It's refreshing.
It's good.
It's delicious.
Is it strong?
It's good.
It's pear.
It's peach.
Peach is delicious.
You said you wanted to eat pear.
It's really peach.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
It's cute.
It's delicious.
It's good.
Did you eat the pear milk?
I didn't eat it.
I did.
Wait a minute.
I want to take a picture of both.
Can you take a picture of both?
It's backlight.
It's dark.
The vanilla is delicious.
The light is good.
It's backlight.
It was a good feeling for a moment.
It's a good feeling.
It's a good feeling now.
Let's go.
It's delicious.
It's fresh.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
I feel the strawberry.
You are cute.
It's a journey to be cute.
The sisters are cute.
It's good.
It's a protector.
It's good for people who come to Hexaheim.
Please take care of your body temperature.
It's especially hot in the summer.
It's said that it's not hot because it's snowy in the Far East.
Isn't it?
It's hot in the summer.
It's cold in the summer.
I understand.
I want you to know that it's hot in the Far East.
That's why fruits grow deliciously.
It's simple.
I often think that it's different from Akita.
I think it's good even though it's next to me.
I think it's different from Miyagi.
I thought it was a city.
It's a city.
Are you fighting with each other?
Akita is definitely a rural area.
No, Akita is a rural area.
The other day, we went to a meeting.
After the meeting, we were looking at the map.
My town is in such a rural area.
There is a station building in the city of Akita.
There is a station building.
Why did you say that?
It's cute.
It was a rich and happy town.
Rika, can I pat your shoulder?
It's cute.
I thought that all the celebrations I went to were not all.
Don't talk more than this.
It's all right.
Please arrange it.
Thank you very much.
We are heading to Maruichi Ikki.
This year, we are going to the Nogizaka live performance.
It's the time when Sendai Tanabata is close.
We are going to the JR Sendai station.
Sendai Tanabata decoration.
We are going to make it the Nogizaka version.
Thank you very much.
We are going to help decorate it.
Let's go.
Is it here?
It's amazing from the entrance.
It's amazing.
Tanabata decorations are already in place.
It's cute.
It's true.
It's written on the back.
Hello.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
Today, we are going to decorate Sendai station.
We are going to make a flower part.
Thank you very much.
Fold it in half in the middle.
Fold it in half.
Put the wire in the middle.
It's a little loose.
Turn it.
It's my favorite work.
It's nostalgic.
It's a habit to open it to people.
It's easy to use.
It's interesting.
It's okay.
How many do you need to make one?
One?
There are four in Sendai station.
It's one.
It's amazing.
It's amazing how many you can make in a day.
That's right.
It's done.
Rika is fast.
I did it.
It's cute.
Moeka, do your best.
I will do my best.
Moeka will do her best.
Thank you.
This is the second one.
I'm used to it.
The craftsman is so cute.
I'm happy.
You're so good.
I helped my mother a lot.
Both of you are good at it.
I want to be a cameraman forever.
Moeka, do your best.
Moeka, you still have one and a half left.
It's done.
Congratulations.
This is the third one.
This is the fourth one.
This is the fifth one.
What is it?
I can see it.
I drew it big.
I think you can do it.
I drew it with kanji.
I thought it was black.
Is it that?
It's easy to see.
Thank you.
It's done.
Thank you for today.
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
We've been on a lot of PR operations.
Now we're going back to Tokyo.
We're on the Shinkansen.
We're on Yamabiko.
Is it still there?
It's still there.
We have another one, which is different from the PR operation.
This year, we will be doing the car-in-car announcement of Yamabiko.
I think we can hear it soon.
We will hear it and go back to Tokyo.
Sayori-san is also talking.
I'm also talking.
I'm talking about Miyagi.
It's me.
It's a good voice.
I'm happy.
It's amazing.
It's not the first voice.
Is this the first time?
It's the first time.
It's a gentle voice.
It's a soft voice.
It's a good voice.
It makes you excited.
A lot of members will be talking to us.
The other day, the bus was next to Mirine.
It was me.
I'm Mirine.
It was here.
It's cute.
Mirine is amazing.
Who is next?
Let's play a game that matches the voice.
Listen to the voice.
Who is next?
There is a field.
Thank you for using JR East Japan.
I'm sorry.
The next stop is Fukushima.
I'm scared.
I'm going to slide.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm scared.
I'm going to slide.
Red and blue are cute.
It's over.
I don't want to touch my beauty.
It's cute.
Can you wink?
I can.
Riku is not good at it.
It's cute.
Riku.
It's limited to live performances.
I'm sorry.
It's done.
It's cute.
I can't do it twice.
It's done.
My eyes are shaking.
It's cute.
Thank you for using JR East Japan.
It's nothing.
I knew Nogizaka was a kind group since I was a fan.
I knew it.
When I joined the group,
all the seniors said they were kind.
I knew it when I first joined the group.
I'm happy.
I think it's something that can be passed on.
It's a good ending.
It's not over yet.
It's over.
It's interesting that it's not appropriate.
I don't know if I can convey it.
It's super appropriate.
But I'm thinking about it.
I'm thinking about it when it comes to activities.
I'm happy that I'm able to get out of it.
It was interesting.
I came in because I wanted Ikeda-san.
Ikeda-san.
I knew it.
I knew it for sure.
It's a good ending.
It was a good ending.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
It was a fun trip to Miyagi.
The tour and Miyagi.
Let's do our best.
Tohoku Sisters.
It's Tohoku.
Are we going to Sisters?
I don't know.
I don't know if we can go home.
It was Tohoku Sisters.
Please subscribe, like, and comment.
Thank you for watching.
Bye bye.